{
  "students": [
    {
      "username": "Mostafa",
      "email": "mm@gmail.com",
      "password": "123",
      "subjects": [
        {
          "name": "الرياضيات",
          "id": "d8e0",
          "degree": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "اللغة الانجليزية",
          "id": "7f80",
          "degree": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "test",
          "id": "658c",
          "degree": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "kk",
          "id": "6ecc",
          "degree": 2
        }
      ],
      "id": "89b4"
    }
  ],
  "doctor": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "email": "admin@admin.com",
      "password": "123",
      "id": "1"
    }
  ],
  "subjects": [
    {
      "name": "الرياضيات",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "80-56",
          "answer1": "66",
          "answer2": "66",
          "answer3": "446",
          "answer4": "44",
          "correctAnswer": "66"
        },
        {
          "question": "50+34",
          "answer1": "33",
          "answer2": "52",
          "answer3": "55",
          "answer4": "55",
          "correctAnswer": "55"
        }
      ],
      "id": "d8e0"
    },
    {
      "id": "eed9",
      "name": "الاحصاء",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "20+33",
          "answer1": "22",
          "answer2": "22",
          "answer3": "44",
          "answer4": "23",
          "correctAnswer": "22"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "7f80",
      "name": "اللغة الانجليزية",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "?wwwww",
          "answer1": "ed",
          "answer2": "dd",
          "answer3": "ff",
          "answer4": "ff",
          "correctAnswer": "ed"
        }
      ]
    },11
    {
      "id": "e7c8",
      "name": "الكورس",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "ث4",
          "answer1": "44",
          "answer2": "4",
          "answer3": "55",
          "answer4": "4",
          "correctAnswer": "4"
        },
        {
          "question": "تعديل",
          "answer1": "6ف",
          "answer2": "فف",
          "answer3": "غغ",
          "answer4": "فف",
          "correctAnswer": "6ف"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "test",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "test",
          "answer1": "1",
          "answer2": "2",
          "answer3": "3",
          "answer4": "4",
          "correctAnswer": "1"
        },
        {
          "question": "edit",
          "answer1": "e",
          "answer2": "r",
          "answer3": "t",
          "answer4": "y",
          "correctAnswer": "r"
        }
      ],
      "id": "658c"
    },
    {
      "id": "6ecc",
      "name": "kk",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "kk",
          "answer1": "k",
          "answer2": "k",
          "answer3": "k",
          "answer4": "k",
          "correctAnswer": "k"
        },
        {
          "question": "g",
          "answer1": "g",
          "answer2": "g",
          "answer3": "g",
          "answer4": "g",
          "correctAnswer": "g"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "hgplg",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "gsd",
          "answer1": "gdg",
          "answer2": "gdg",
          "answer3": "gdg",
          "answer4": "dg",
          "correctAnswer": "gdg"
        }
      ],
      "id": "cdfe"
    }
  ],
  "login": [
    {
      "username": "Mostafa",
      "role": "students",
      "userId": "89b4",
      "id": "1"
    }
  ]
}
